https://dupsies.com/Dstore/privacy.php

Open for Online orders! Free shipping on orders of $100 or more. For local shoppers,
we are accepting Curb-side pickup orders! Order online and pickup between 2pm and 5pm Mon - Sat.
Search by Size
WomenXXS(0)XS(2)XS(4)Small(6)Small(8)Medium(10)Medium(12)Large(14)Large(16)XL(18)XL(20)2X(22)2X(24)PLUS - 3X(22W)PLUS - 3X(24W)PLUS - 4X(26WE)PLUS - 4X(28WE)PLUS - 5X(32WE)PLUS - 5X(34WE)X-SmallSmallMediumLargeXL2X3X4X5XCustomPLUS - 6X (36-38)PLUS - 7X (40-42)MenX-SmallSmallMediumLargeXL2XL3XL4XL5XL6XL7XLChildren1 yearNewborn to 6 months1/2 years2 years3 years4 years5 years6 years7 years8 years9 years10 years11 years12 years13 years14 yearsHats20 Inches - Size 51 1/2 cm (small)20 1/2 Inches - Size 52 1/2 cm (small)21 Inches - Size 6 5/8 (Small)21 1/2 Inches - Size 6 3/4 (Small)22 Inches - Size 7 (medium)22 1/2 Inches -
Size 7 1/8 (medium)23 Inches - Size 7 3/8 (large)23 1/2 Inches - Size 7 1/2 (XL)23 3/4 Inches - Size 7 1/2 (XL)24 Inches - Size 7 5/8 (XL)24 1/2 Inches - Size 7 3/4 (XXL)25 Inches - Size 63.5 cm (XXL)25.5 Inches - Size 8 1/8 (XXXL)26 Inches - Size 64.5 cm (XXXL)
Headwraps/ HatsAfrican Head wraps  African Print Head wraps(Cotton)  African Headbands for Ladies  African Pre-tied Head Wraps/Hats  Aso OkeCrowntex (SuperNet)DamaskNetSilkYoruba Traditional Aso-oke  Cotton African Head wrap  Gele Head wrapSego Gele Head wrap  Kente-Handwoven  Mud Cloth Head Wraps/ Shawls  Print Head wraps
African Hats, Caps, Kente Sashes
Kente StoreKente Store
Dashiki StoreDashiki Store
WomenWomen  African Top and Skirt  African Top and Wrapper  African Dresses and Jumpsuits  African Skirts and Wrappers  African Women's Pants and Shorts  African Female Tops  African Head
Wrap/Hats  African Jewelry  African Print Purses  African Robe for Women  African Shoes and Sandals for Wo
African Clothing Top and Skirt  African Print Skirt Set  Brocade Skirt Set  French Lace Skirt Set  Lace Skirt Set  Plain Cotton African Top Skirt
African Pants for WomenAfrican Print BagsAfrican Robes for WomenAfrican Skirts, Shorts, WrappersAfrican Wrapper Set  African Print Wrapper Set  African Velvet Wrapper Set  Asooke Wrapper Set  Brocade Wrapper Set  Lace Wrapper Set  Others
African DressesAfrican Head wraps  African Print Head wraps(Cotton)  African Headbands for Ladies  African Pre-tied Head Wraps/Hats  Aso OkeCrowntex (SuperNet)DamaskNetSilkYoruba Traditional Aso-oke  Cotton African Head wrap  Gele Head wrapSego Gele Head wrap  Kente-Handwoven  Mud Cloth Head Wraps/ Shawls  Print Head wraps
African Caftan(BouBou)  African Print  Brocade Caftan  Others
African Female Pants SetAfrican Female Tops
MenMen  African Cuff Links  Dashiki | Dupsie's  African Dashiki  African Grand BouBou (Agbada)  African Hats and Sashes  African Ties and Bow-Ties  T-Shirts  African Men's Pants  Men's Sandals  Men's Jewelry
Dashiki  African Print Dashiki Shirts  African Print Shirts  African Velvet Isiagu Shirt  Brocade Dashiki Shirts  Cotton Dashiki Shirts  Mudcloth Shirts
African Dashiki  African Dashiki Top and Pants  Dashiki African Print  Dashiki Brocade Pant Set
Agbada (Grand Boubou)  Agbada Brocade  Agbada others  Aso-Oke Agbada Grand Boubou  Print Grand Boubou Agbada
African Hats, Caps, Kente SashesAfrican Ties and Bow-TiesT-Shirts  Black History T-Shirts
Tie Dye T-ShirtsSandals
ChildrenAfrican Children, Boys, Girls  Boys  Girls
Accessories/ Fabric/ OtherMud Cloth (Bogolan) StoreAfrican ArtAfrican Fabric  African Cotton Fabric  African Mud Cloth Fabric  African Lace Fabrics  African Print Fabrics  African Velvet Fabric
African Print BagsAfrican Wedding Fashion AttiresDressy Shoes For WomenTradtional African FansTrendy African Print ShoesAfrican Jewelry  African Dashiki Buttons  African Jewelry Sets  African Waist Beads  Bracelets /BanglesWomen  Earrings  NecklacesWomen  African Beads Jewelry
African Ties and Bow-TiesAfrican SandalsAfrican Clothing (Embroidery)African FansGift Vouchers
Dupsies EXclusiveDupsie's ExclusiveNew ArrivalsSize ChartLog InShopping Cart (0 items) CheckoutContact Us
0
Home » Store » Privacy Notice
New Arrivals |  Size Chart |  My Account  |  Cart Contents  | Checkout
Categories
Headwraps/ HatsAfrican Head wrapsAfrican Print Head wraps(Cotton)African Headbands for LadiesAfrican Pre-tied Head Wraps/HatsAso OkeCrowntex (SuperNet)DamaskNetSilkYoruba Traditional Aso-okeCotton African Head wrapGele Head wrapSego Gele Head wrapKente-HandwovenMud Cloth Head Wraps/ ShawlsPrint Head wrapsAfrican Hats, Caps, Kente SashesKente StoreKente StoreDashiki StoreDashiki StoreWomenWomenAfrican Top and SkirtAfrican Top and WrapperAfrican Dresses and JumpsuitsAfrican Skirts and WrappersAfrican Women's Pants and ShortsAfrican Female TopsAfrican Head
Wrap/HatsAfrican JewelryAfrican Print PursesAfrican Robe for WomenAfrican Shoes and Sandals for WoAfrican Clothing Top and SkirtAfrican Print Skirt SetBrocade Skirt SetFrench Lace Skirt SetLace Skirt SetPlain Cotton African Top SkirtAfrican Pants for WomenAfrican Print BagsAfrican Robes for WomenAfrican Skirts, Shorts, WrappersAfrican Wrapper SetAfrican Print Wrapper SetAfrican Velvet Wrapper SetAsooke Wrapper SetBrocade Wrapper SetLace Wrapper SetOthersAfrican DressesAfrican Head wrapsAfrican Print Head wraps(Cotton)African Headbands for LadiesAfrican Pre-tied Head Wraps/HatsAso OkeCrowntex (SuperNet)DamaskNetSilkYoruba Traditional Aso-okeCotton African Head wrapGele Head wrapSego Gele Head wrapKente-HandwovenMud Cloth Head Wraps/ ShawlsPrint Head wrapsAfrican Caftan(BouBou)African PrintBrocade CaftanOthersAfrican Female Pants SetAfrican Female TopsMenMenAfrican Cuff LinksDashiki | Dupsie'sAfrican DashikiAfrican Grand BouBou (Agbada)African Hats and SashesAfrican Ties and Bow-TiesT-ShirtsAfrican Men's PantsMen's SandalsMen's JewelryDashikiAfrican Print Dashiki ShirtsAfrican Print ShirtsAfrican Velvet Isiagu ShirtBrocade Dashiki ShirtsCotton Dashiki ShirtsMudcloth ShirtsAfrican DashikiAfrican Dashiki Top and PantsDashiki African PrintDashiki Brocade Pant SetAgbada (Grand Boubou)Agbada BrocadeAgbada othersAso-Oke Agbada Grand BoubouPrint Grand Boubou AgbadaAfrican Hats, Caps, Kente SashesAfrican Ties and Bow-TiesT-ShirtsBlack History T-ShirtsTie Dye T-ShirtsSandalsChildrenAfrican Children, Boys, GirlsBoysGirlsAccessories/ Fabric/ OtherMud Cloth (Bogolan) StoreAfrican ArtAfrican FabricAfrican Cotton FabricAfrican Mud Cloth FabricAfrican Lace FabricsAfrican Print FabricsAfrican Velvet FabricAfrican Print BagsAfrican Wedding Fashion AttiresDressy Shoes For WomenTradtional African FansTrendy African Print ShoesAfrican JewelryAfrican Dashiki ButtonsAfrican Jewelry SetsAfrican Waist BeadsBracelets /BanglesWomenEarringsNecklacesWomenAfrican Beads JewelryAfrican Ties and Bow-TiesAfrican SandalsAfrican Clothing (Embroidery)African FansGift VouchersDupsies EXclusiveDupsie's Exclusive
Featured
Orange Blue Print high wasited Long Pleated Skirt-DP3310SK$49.99
What's New?
Washoge Roselyn Kente African Print Sports Bra for Women$28.99
Privacy Notice
Your personal data is safe
Secured by SSL
Cookie storage
Your personal data is safeDupsie's respects your privacy. Any information you provide us is only used to process your order.
We will NEVER share any personal information including name, address, email, phone number or credit card information with other companies or people apart from giving your address to our shipping partners.
You can sign up anytime for our newsletters or product notifications, and you can change these subscriptions without notice in your Account area or contacting
us.top
Secured by SSL
As soon as you enter personal data, you are secured by the 256 bit encryption protocol provided by the SSL certificate of our hosting company. You will notice the padlock sign in the bottom right corner of your browser to confirm SSL is working correctly. All URLs in this secured area will start with 'https://', while regular pages start with 'http://'.top
Cookie storage
We use short term cookies to save your shopping cart while you are browsing our pages. These per-session cookies are deleted as soon as your session expires after you leave our website.
Shopping Cart
0 items
Search
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Shop By PriceUnder $10.00From $10.00 to $20.00From $21.00 to $30.00From $31.00 to $50.00From $51.00 to $70.00From $71.00 to $100.00Above $100.00Show all price ranges
Specials
African Beads Necklace and Bracelet Set-DPIL501$69.99$49.99
Testimonials
"All of the outfits are beautiful"...Read more...louise: North Lauderdale, FL
Follow US
Live Support
Product Reviews
I am pleased with this product. The richness in color and sm ..
Affiliate Program
Affiliate InformationAffiliate Program FAQAffiliate Log In
Gift Vouchers
Friday 11 December, 2020
Contact Us | Shipping & Returns | Specials | Product Reviews | Privacy Notice | Conditions of Use | Voucher FAQ | Point Program FAQ | Track a Return | Map | Downloadable catalog | Testimonials | Site Map | Featured Products | Facebook App Privacy Policy |
Call us Toll Free: 1-855-DUPSIES (387-7437)
Tel: 1.770.948.2220
Business Hours: 10:30 AM to 6.00 PM EST. Mon-Sat
Copyright © 2020 Dupsie's Inc
This website uses cookies. By using this website you consent to our use of these cookies. For more information visit our
Privacy Policy.
Accept
